欢迎喜欢的朋友加入familyguy百度贴吧共同讨论
或加FG粉丝交流 QQ群 165859780
♪ It seems today that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a... Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
Family Guy 10x04
Stewie Goes for a Drive
Stewie开车记
中文字幕: zurica 校对: wudixny 注释: wudixny zurica 后期: zurica 压制: zurica @familyguy贴吧字幕组
医生给我打针的时候我很勇敢
I was very brave when the doctor gave me that shot,
对不对 Lois
wasn't I, Lois?
是的 Peter 你很勇敢
Yes, Peter, you were very brave.
即使我知道他马上要给我那一针了
Even when I knew that he was gonna give me the shot,
我也依然直视着他的双眼
I just k-kept looking at him in the eye
轻松地和他谈论暑期的安排
and talking to him about my summer plans.
你做的很棒
You did very good.
你看 Peter 没那么吓人吧
See, Peter? It wasn't so bad.
没错 只是在候诊室中不得不坐在
Yeah, except for having to sit next to
那个大呼小叫的自闭症女人边上 让我不自在
that screaming autistic lady in the waiting room.
我不知道你想要什么 我不知道怎么帮你
I don't know what you want! I don't know how to help!
嗨 打扰一下
Hi, there. Excuse me.
我好像迷路了 你们能帮帮我吗
I seem to be lost. Can you guys help me?
哦 老天
Oh, my God.
你是Ryan Reynolds吗
Are you Ryan Reynolds?
加拿大演员
主演过《假结婚》和《互换身体》
From The Proposal and The Change-Up
还有一大堆即将面世的作品 没错 是我
and a ton of upcoming stuff? Yeah, that's me.
我正要去新港 有点绕糊涂了
I was on my way to Newport and I kind of got turned around.
当然没问题了 Reynolds先生 我们很乐意给你指点方向
Of course, Mr. Reynolds, we'd be happy to give you directions.
你上138号公路前往詹姆斯敦桥
You take 138 to the Jamestown Bridge,
然后沿着…
and you're gonna follow the...
那边有辆消防车
There's a fire truck.
是的 我看见了 Peter
Yes, I see it, Peter.
是消防车
It's a fire truck.
过了那座桥 沿着路标走
And after the bridge, just follow the signs.
谢谢
Thanks.
哎 你的胳膊怎么了
Hey, what happened to your arm?
我去看医生了 检查了一下胆固醇水平
I just went to the doctor, got my cholesterol checked.
哇 一个二十多岁的棒小伙儿
Wow, why does a guy in his 20s
需要检查胆固醇水平吗
need to get his cholesterol checked?
喔 别说笑了
Oh, come on, now.
哦 对了 我还没问你姓名呢
Oh, hey, I never got your name.
呃 Peter Peter Griffin
Uh, Peter. Peter Griffin.
我叫Lo…
And I'm Lo...
回头见 Peter
Catch you later, Peter.
哇 他人可真好
Wow, he was really nice.
可不像我上次遇见的那个贱人Shelley Duvall
Not like when I met that bitch Shelley Duvall.
美国女演员 出演过电影《闪灵》《大力水手》
嗨 我是Shelley Duvall
Hi, I'm Shelley Duvall.
很高兴见到你
Very nice to meet you.
有什么了不起的
Big deal.
径直就冲我走过来了 好像我迫不及待想见她似的
Came right up to me, like I was just dying to meet her.
Peter 别把那件事放在心上了
Peter, you're gonna have to let that one go.
嗨 Janetti夫人 我来接Stewie回家
Hi, Mrs. Janetti. I'm here to pick up Stewie.
哦 好的 Brian 他在娱乐室里和Gavin玩呢
Oh, sure, Brian. He's in the playroom with Gavin.
Gavin 多傻逼的名字
Gavin- that's a stupid name.
幼儿园里没人喜欢你
And nobody likes you at school.
你长大了肯定很丑
You're gonna be ugly when you grow up.
你家里的东西都是便宜货
And everything in your house is cheap.
在这儿都能闻见穷酸味了
And it smells in here.
哦 你来了 Brian
Oh, hey, Brian.
再见
Bye!
真有趣
That was fun.
我喜欢Gavin
I like Gavin.
哦吔 这真是首好歌
Oh, yay! This is such a great song.
- 真的吗 - 没错 真的
- Really? - Yeah, really.
我没必要针对你才说Carrie Underwood的好话
I don't have to defend Carrie Underwood to you.
美国著名乡村女歌手 曾五次获得格莱美奖
你不喜欢她 她也很优秀
She is doing just fine without you.
Brian 我要坐在车里把这首歌听完
Brian, I'm just going to sit in the car till the song's over.
好吧 不过别太久了 会把电耗光的
All right, but don't take to long; it'll drain the battery.
哎呀 闭嘴吧 不会把电用光的
Oh, shut up. It's not draining the battery.
♪ 我用球棒打碎了前车灯 ♪
♪ I took a Louisville Slugger to both headlights ♪
这首歌是《Before He Cheats》
♪ 我在车胎上都捅了洞 ♪
♪ I slashed a hole in all four tires ♪
♪ 也许下一次他欺骗前会考虑考虑 ♪
♪ Maybe next time he'll think before he cheats ♪
我真该去演《欢乐合唱团》的
I should be on Glee.
我真该去演《欢乐合唱团》
I should be on Glee!
♪ 也许下个女孩就不必再心碎受伤 ♪
♪ I might've saved a little trouble for the next girl... ♪
哦 老天
Oh, my God.
我刚才是开车了哈
I just drove.
太神奇了
That was amazing.
我会开车
I can drive!
现在我可以开车慢慢驶过前女友的公寓门口了
Now I can do a slow cruise past my ex-girlfriend's apartment.
11:45了 灯还亮着
11:45 and the lights are on.
现在喜欢开着灯做爱了吗 臭婊子
Doing it with the lights on now, whore?
不介意看到那男人的身体了吗
Don't mind looking at his body?
不过我还是那么爱你
I love you so much, though.
Lois 那条瞳孔有好几种颜色的狗又来了
Lois, that dog with the different colored eyes is back.
呃 真恶心
Ew, and gross!
好像它还勃起了
It looks like he's got a boner.
Peter 别管它
Peter, just leave him alone.
不 Bob Barker这些年来
No, this is what Bob Barker's been
游戏节目主持人 丧妻后成为一个动物权益保护者
一直在谈论这个
talking about all these years.
滚开 滚
Go on! Get!
滚远点 奇怪的屌狗
Get out of here, weird boner dog!
哎哟 看看这是谁呀
Hey, look who it is!
嗨 Ryan Reynolds
Hey, Ryan Reynolds.
你怎么在Cleveland的房子里
What are you doing in Cleveland's house?
好吧 说来你也许不信 他们准备
Well, believe it or not, they've decided
不去新港而在Quahog拍我的电影了
to shoot my movie in Quahog instead of Newport.
我饰演希特勒 不过是年轻版的希特勒
I'm playing Hitler, but he's a young Hitler
而且他有着极棒的身材
and he's got a rocking body.
所以叫"型"特勒
It's called Hotler.
哈 看来我的腰包又要少7块钱了(看电影)
Ha! Color me seven bucks lighter.
我真的很高兴咱们能成为邻居
Hey, I'm so excited that we're gonna be neighbors.
咱们绝对应该一起出去玩玩
We should totally hang out.
好呀 挺不错的
Yeah, that'd be great.
哎哟 我真丢人
Okay, I'm embarrassed.
在这儿站了半天 连衬衫都没穿
I'm standing out here without a shirt on
睡裤的腰边都滑到屁股上了
and my pajama bottoms are riding insanely low on my hips.
哎 你一般挣多少钱
Hey, how much money you make?
你觉得应该够买一件衬衫了吧 是不是
You'd think enough for a shirt, right?
既然今晚我要开一个乔迁庆祝会
So I'm having this housewarming thing tonight,
希望你能大驾光临
and I'd love it if you came by.
嗯 听起来很棒
Yeah. It sounds great
什么事都比我家周五晚上做的那些事要好
Anything beats what goes on at my house Friday nights.
嗨 Lois 你们在干嘛
Hey, Lois, what's going on here?
哦 这是我们的读书俱乐部 Peter
Oh, it's my book club, Peter.
一起来吧
Come join us.
好的
Oh, okay!
好吧 来看看 新小说 新小说 新小说
All right, let's see, new novel, new novel, new novel.
应该写什么呢 写关于什么的呢
What's it about? What's it about?
一个人…
A guy...
一个人失去了一切
a guy who loses everything,
但是在加拿大找回了自我
but finds his soul in Canada.
好吧 咱们开始写了
All right, we're cooking now.
写吧
Cooking now.
整本书就是一封电子邮件
And the whole book is an e-mail
写给他过世的女儿
to his daughter, who's dead.
他的名字就叫Norm Hull(肉体凡胎)好了
And his name will be Norm Hull.
因为他只是个普通人
Because he's just a normal guy.
不过并不是每个人都明白这点
But not everybody will get that.
那还是留给百年后的学者们去研究吧
That's just for e scholars a hundred years from now.
好的 Rupert 你准备好乘车兜风了吗
Okay, Rupert, you ready to go for a drive?
老天 Rupert 太令人激动了
Oh, my God, Rupert, this is such a thrill.
你看我 在开车吔
Look at me, I'm driving!
我在开一辆真实的车
I'm driving a real car!
我自己都不相信
I don't believe it!
好吧 我觉着咱们应该放些音乐
Well, I'd say we need to put on some tunes.
嗨 欢迎继续收听FM97.1频道的"鸡鸡与屁屁"节目
Hey, welcome back to Weenie and The Butt on 97.1.
此节目参见S05E02 S和B那集也去电台搞了个类似的节目
♪ 97.1 ♪
唔 鸡鸡与屁屁
Ooh, Weenie and The Butt.
听起来像成年人的节目
Just like the grown-ups listen to.
请欣赏由Justin Bieber和Ludacris为您带来的《宝贝》
And that was "Baby" by Justin Bieber featuring Ludacris,
后者是饶舌歌手 演员 出演过《速度与激情》系列
也就意味着 我们将送出Justin Bieber的演唱会门票
which means it's time to give away some Justin Bieber tickets.
没错 屁屁
Oh, that's right, Butt.
第五个讲电话打入演播间的听众将会赢得这些门票
Our fifth caller will ween those tickets.
哎 你猜怎么着 Rupert
Hey, you know what, Rupert?
你知道我该怎么做 才能像个傻逼一样吗
You know what I should do, just, like, as a goof?
我应该去尽力赢取这些门票 这样我就能
I should try to win those Justin Bieber tickets just so I can,
比如 撕掉它们或者用它们去看演唱会
like, tear them up or use them to go to t concert.
哦 通了 Rupert 通了呢
Oh, it's ringing, Rupert, it's ringing.
我太紧张了 他们可都是名人
I'm too nervous; they're celebrities.
你来跟他们说
You talk to them.
老天呐 老天呐
Oh, God. Oh, my God.
我麻烦大了
I'm in so much trouble.
恭喜你 你是第五个打入电话的人
Congratulations, you're caller number five.
你将会见到Justin Bieber了
You're going to see Justin Bieber!
万能的春哥啊
Oh, sweet Jesus!
太好了 Jesse 我赢了
Yes! Jesse, I won!
Jesse是恋童老头Herbert养的老狗
永不言弃
Never say never!
Justin Bieber有一首同名歌
天呐 天呐
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
我的天呐 Brian会杀了我的
Oh, my God, Brian's gonna be so mad at me.
我该怎么办 好吧 就这样吧
What am I gonna do? Okay, it's all right.
我找点油漆把这些缺口都刷一刷
I'll just get a little bit of paint and cover up the dents.
缺乏魅力的女人总是这么干的
Unattractive women do it all the time.
你今天看起来真漂亮 Carol
You look pretty today, Carol.
谢谢
Thanks.
大概是衣服和化妆品的功劳吧
It's probably just the dress and the makeup.
呃 近了一看
Ah, now that I look closer,
没错 确实如此
yeah, I think that's what it is, too.
嗨 你赴约了
Hey, you made it!
还带来了一位朋友
And you brought a friend.
太好了
Great.
我是他妻子 Lois
I'm his wife, Lois.
我们其实在某天见过
We actually met the other day.
哦 抱歉 我每天见的人太多了
Oh, sorry, I- I meet so many people.
不过说了你肯定也不明白
But there's really no way you could know that.
没错 她就是个家庭妇女 啥也不懂
Yeah, she's a housewife, she don't know.
随你怎么说
Whatever.
你这儿有酒吗
You got booze in here?
是因为我 还是她 才造成了这种尴尬的气氛
Is it me, or did she just make that weird?
别这么说 肯定不怪你啦
Please. It was definitely not you.
哎 这件衬衫是不是太紧身了
Hey, is this shirt too tight?
我感觉有点不好意思
I'm feeling really self-conscious.
没有的事
No, not at all.
- 这么说 看起来还不错 - 嗯 不错
- So it-it looks good like this? - Yeah, it looks good.
谢谢
Thanks.
我不知道说什么好了
I don't know what to say.
哎 我有一些 一些 那个
Hey, I got, I got, like,
好莱坞的内部问题要问你
an insider Hollywood question for you.
是不是 呃 "L.A."的缩写有什么含义
Is, um, is "L.A." short for something?
LA除了指洛杉矶外还可以指
舔亲一个人的腹部并用舌头划出LA字母的形状
哈 你真有喜感
Ha! You're a riot.
哎 这一切究竟是怎么回事
Hey, hey, so what's all this about,
为什么Quahog的每个人都喜欢玩"挠痒痒"
everyone in Quahog likes to tickle fight?
那究竟是什么
What is that?
什么 我从没听说过啊
What? I never heard that.
呃 显然 有这么回事
Yeah, apparently it's, like, a thing.
- 是吗 - 是的
- It is? - Yeah.
而且 别人还说那些假装
I mean, they also said that people who pretend
没听过这种游戏的人都是瘪三
not to have heard of it are chicken.
好吧 我可不是瘪三
Well, I ain't no chicken.
一比零
One-nothing!
二比零
No, two-nothing!
三比零
Three-nothing!
比赛结束 比赛结束
Fight over! Fight over!
哈 看来你要恶补许多知识啊
Wow, you got a lot of catching up to do,
明晚黑了灯之后我教你 怎么样
and tomorrow night in the dark, huh?
黑了灯
In the dark?
是的 如果你不介意
Yeah, if you say so.
只要别在我的下腹部挠痒痒了
Just don't tickle me in my lower abdomen.
我那里超级怕痒
I'm super ticklish there.
下腹部
Lower abdomen.
你肯定会后悔自己透露了这个小秘密
You're gonna wish you never said that.
这么问也许很唐突
This might be totally off the wall,
你在周四晚上有什么事做吗
but are you doing anything Thursday night?
虽说你可能有安排了
You probably have plans, anyway.
你知道吗…
You know what...
还是不提了 不提了 不提了
Forget it, forget it, forget it.
噗 太紧张
Blah. Nervous.
其实呢 Ryan 大多数人第一眼见到我
You know, Ryan, most people take one look at me
都会假定我有安排了 所以从来没人约我出去
and just assume that I have plans, so I never get asked out.
不过通常我没有安排 那么好的
But I-I frequently don't have plans, so yes,
我愿意在周四晚上陪你做点什么
I would love to do something with you on Thursday night.
太好了 老天 现在是你最好的时机
Yes! Oh, my God, right now would be the worst time
来挠我的下腹部了
for you to tickle my lower abdomen,
因为我举手欢呼所以它露出来了
because it's so exposed 'cause I'm cheering.
吔 周四晚上
Yeah, Thursday night!
哈 你的大嘴巴给你招来麻烦了吧
Aw, your big mouth just got you in trouble.
啊 我输了
Aw, I lose.
- Peter一分 你零分 - 啊 我又输了
- Peter one, you zero. - Oh, I lose again.
- Peter两分 你零分 - 你很熟练了嘛
- Peter two, you zero. - You've been practicing.
现在请继续收看七十年代颓废科幻电影的结局
We now return to the end of a depressing 1970s sci-fi movie
此段恶搞了美国1976年的科幻电影《Logan's Run》
由穿着高领衣服的人主演
starring a guy in a turtleneck.
我们已经跑得够远了
We've gone far enough.
我们到这儿应该可以逃脱公司的魔掌了
I think we're safe from The Corporation here.
Adzin 你看
Adzin, look!
不会是这样的
It can't be.
不
No!
我们永远无法打败公司
We'll never defeat The Corporation!
他们赢了
They've won!
只有一种方式可以解脱 Adzin
There is one way, Adzin.
给自己来一枪吧
You can shoot yourself.
如果那是唯一的方式 我只好认命了
If it's the only way, I must.
怎么回事
What the hell?!
Stewie 给我滚出来
Stewie, get out here!
看看这个
Look at this.
你知道这是怎么回事吗
Do you know anything about this?
什么事
A- About what?
你是说今天美好的天气吗…
About what a beautiful day it...
哎呀 天呐 太奇怪了
Oh, my God, that is surprising.
唔 我不得不打断自己刚才说的那句话
Oh, I had to stop that last sentence in the middle
我太意外了
because I was so surprised.
- 发生什么事了 - 哼 我不知道
- What happened? - Gee, I don't know.
你知道发生什么事了吗
Do you know what happened?
真抱歉 你说什么
I'm sorry, w-what was that?
我想起了另一件好笑的事
I- I was laughing at that funny thing
你某天晚上吃饭的时候讲的
you said at dinner the other night.
什么好笑的事
What funny thing?
呃 你记不记得你讲过
Um, y-you remember what you said
关于Lois的 呃 "烂焗土豆"
about Lois's, um, "potatoes au rotten"?
"Potatoes au gratin(焗土豆)"是法国菜
表面是一层松脆的奶酪或面包屑
呵 还以为别人没听见呢
Huh. Didn't think anybody heard that.
当时你怎么不笑呢
Wish you'd laughed at the time.
我的车究竟TM的怎么回事
W- What the hell happened to my car?!
呃 我不知道吔 老兄 不过还好
Well, I don't know, man, but the good news is,
并不像看起来那么糟糕 Brian
it-it doesn't look all that bad, Brian.
是不是这个缺口
It's just, it's that spot right there
让你看起来不爽 是吗
that's upsetting you, right?
Stewie 我知道是你弄的
Stewie, I know it was you.
你的"土豆笑话"其实挺烂的
Your potato joke was terrible.
我不敢相信你开我的车出去了
I can't believe you drove my car!
你这么乱搞会闹出人命的
You could have gotten yourself killed!
我得告诉你爹妈
I'm gonna have to tell Peter and Lois.
不 不 你不能告诉他们
No! No, you can't tell them!
那样我麻烦就大了
I'll be in so much trouble!
Stewie 我必须那样做
Stewie, I have to.
虽然 以前我总罩着你
All right, I have covered for you
好多次了 可这次不行
plenty of times before, but not this time.
这是很危险的事
This is very dangerous,
我得确保你再也不会这么做了
and have to make sure you never do it again.
我不会的 我发誓
I won't, I swear!
Stewie 别闹了
Stewie, calm down.
有时候在生活中你必须承受所发生的事
Sometimes in life you just have to accept what's coming to you.
就像竞猜者们在《价格竞猜》节目中
Like the contestant who gets the lesser showcase
一个老牌游戏节目 猜对价格后便能获得该商品
之前提到的Bob Barker曾主持过该节目30多年
被分到了不值钱的展示品
on The Price is Right.
Lindsay 你的展示品
Lindsay, your showcase
都是关于休闲类的
is all about relaxation.
还有什么比你全新的吊床更令人放松的
And what better place to relax than in your brand-new hammock?!
Swingway牌结实舒适的吊床可以把自家庭院
This sturdy and portable hammock from Swingway turns any patio
变成热带天堂
into a tropical paradise.
而且你在后院享受的时候
And you can entertain yourself on your patio
还可以用粉笔画画
by drawing with chalk!
没错 Pratt & Millwood牌的八种颜色粉笔
Yes, Pratt and Millwood eight-color pastel chalk
可以把你家庭院装点成热带艺术工作室
will turn your patio into a tropical art studio.
不过你得揣上自己的粉笔
But you'll have to pack your chalk
因为你还要花上
because you're going to be staying
六天七夜
six days and seven nights
呆在特拉华州威尔明顿的父母家中
at your parents' house in Wilmington, Delaware!
一个工业发达 污染严重的城市 这里应该是指到该地的一次旅游机会
这个环节我放弃了
I moved my abortion for this.
店名中的马拉喀什(Marrakech)是摩洛哥古都
呃 多谢你带我出来吃晚饭 Ryan
Um, hey, thanks for taking me out to dinner, Ryan,
不过我得说 这饭菜看着怪怪的
but I got to say, this food looks a little weird.
呃 Peter 摩洛哥饭菜就是这个鸟样子
Aw, Peter, Moroccan food is the jizz.
jizz在俚语中也有精液的意思 这里可能是性暗示
我不知道 看起来会让我吃了以后放某种屁
I don't know. Looks like it might give me the kind of farts
就像我上次吃那个墨西哥饭菜一样
I get from eating Mexican food.
(西班牙语) 当心 臭味来了
Con cuidado es el stinko!
哎 这条裤子看起来还行吧
Hey, do these pants look all right?
有时候我穿着 感觉自己看起来莽撞
Sometimes I put them on, and I'm thinking I look all balls.
不 我觉得还行
No, I think you're good.
你觉得我蛋蛋还行
You think my balls are good?
你可真搞怪
You're so weird.
话说回来还是挺不错的
It's awesome, though.
呃 我…我不懂
Oh, I... I don't know.
哎 你有没有注意到
Hey, have you noticed
镇上的邮差真是个二逼
what a jerk the mailman is in this town?
比如 他就说过
Like, he said there is no way
Peter Griffin 绝不可能当着我的面
Peter Griffin could crush a baby bird
赤脚踩死一只小雏鸟
with his bare foot while I watched.
那个家伙还说了我好多坏话
That guy talks more crap about me.
嗯 唔
Mmm! Oh!
嗯 你得尝尝这个地锅炖羔羊肉
Mmm. You got to taste this lamb tagine.
嗯 给你
Mmm. Here.
不 那个…好意心领了
No, that... no, that's okay.
来嘛 你会喜欢的
Come on, you'll love it.
呃…
Eh...
尝一小口
Just a taste.
那可真是…让人兴奋啊
That was... intense.
就你刚才那样子
What you just did.
好重的…
Lots of...
好重的味儿啊
Lots of flavors.
哎哟
Whoops.
哇哦 心有灵犀啊
Whoa, freeze frame!
接下来会怎样呢
What's gonna happen next?
我想去趟洗手间
I think I got to go to the bathroom.
我该怎么办
What am I gonna do?
我会有大麻烦的
I'm gonna be in so much trouble
要是他们发现我撞毁了Brian的车
when they find out I wrecked Brian's car!
他们很可能会把我流放到西伯利亚去
They'll probably ship me off to Siberia.
这鬼地方 我恨死了
This sucks. I hate it here.
闭嘴
Shut up.
喝点狼奶 看看俄国动画片
Drink wolf milk and watch Russian cartoons.
请继续收看俄罗斯流行卡通《鞋与鞋带》
We now return to popular Russian cartoon, Shoe and Shoelace.
鞋与鞋带
Shoe and Shoelace!
生死与共的好伙伴
One is meaningless without the other!
BGM是苏联国歌《牢不可破的联盟》
好吧 就这样了
Well, that's it.
我别无选择
I have no choice.
我得离家出走
I've got to run away.
也许这就是我自己种下的苦果吧 Rupert
Guess I'm on my own now, Rupert.
尽管前路可能更艰难
It could be worse, though.
不过至少我不会被大街上
At least I'm not getting stabbed
某个莫名其妙的家伙捅一刀
by some random guy on the street.
看到了吧 情况正好相反
See? It's the exact opposite.
Stewie被捅的情节在S09E06发生过
啊 还是发生了
Oh! It happened anyway!
嗨 Stewie 你起床了吗
Hey, Stewie, you up?
这是…
What the...
Brian 我决定离家出走了
Brian, I've decided to run away.
别来找我
Don't come looking for me.
确切地说 别追我到机场
And definitely don't chase me to the airport
在我快登机的时候追到检票口
and catch me at the gate just before I'm about to get on the plane
我可能刚发表了激情的演讲 还收到了鲜花
with, like, an emotional speech and possibly flowers.
比如 要是所有
For example, it would be awful
交通安全管理局的人都围过来
if all the TSA people were gathered around,
TSA = Transportation Security Administration
观看这个激动人心的时刻 那可就糟了
watching this emotional moment,
就连那个拿着扫描器的黑人老太婆也不例外
even the older black female carry-on scanner
她本打算在行李检查口拦住你的
who initially stopped you at the baggage check,
这里是讽刺电影中不合理的煽情段落
可你身后的人跟她说了你的真实意图 于是她说
but who after you told her of your intentions, said,
"去追他吧 孩子" 无耻地忽视了
"Go get him, child," in flagrant disregard
9-11之后新规定的所有安全措施
of all newly-implemented post-9-11 security measures.
如果你要是考虑带上个炸弹盒(伪装成音频播放器)
And if you were considerin bringing a boom box
来放音乐的话 我向你建议这六首歌曲中的一首
to play music, I would suggest any one of these six songs.
所以再说一遍 走开吧
So again, ran away.
别来找我
Don't come after me.
♪ 我要感谢你... ♪
♪ I want to thank you... ♪
Dido的《Thank You》
臭婊子 你们都是
Dirty whores, all of you.
哦 Peter
Oh, hey, Peter.
Lois 我们有麻烦了
Lois, we got a problem.
我觉得Ryan Reynolds爱上我了
I think Ryan Reynolds is in love with me.
什么 别瞎说了
What? Don't be ridiculous.
是真的 昨晚我们一起去吃饭
It's true. Last night we were at this restaurant,
他想要"基"吻我
and he tried to gay kiss me.
跟你说吧 他就是想跟我好
I'm telling you, he wants to get with me.
Peter 得了吧
Peter, come on.
怎么可能每个男人懂穿着 会打扮 爱锻炼
Why would any man dress well, groom himself and lift weights
就是为了和别的男人睡觉
just to sleep with other men?
他不是同性恋
He's not gay.
好吧 我不管你怎么说 他就是喜欢我
Well, I don't care what you say. He likes me.
不过我们确实来电 我…我不否认这一点
And we do have chemistry, I- I won't deny that.
我…我会负责任的
I- I... I will take responsibility
承担自己的那一份责任
from my part in this.
我这就去那边和他说清楚
I'm just gonna go over there and let him down easy.
哦 Snooki死了
Oh, Snooki died.
拉丁女演员Nicole Polizzi的绰号 没死
《南方公园》曾在S14E09里讽刺过她 她爆了Cartman菊花
终点站
Last stop.
什么 这不是机场啊
What? This isn't the airport.
老天呐 Rupert
Oh, my God, Rupert!
我们得离开这里
We've got to get out of here!
啊 我日
Aah! Damn it!
哦 不 不
Oh, no, no.
小孩儿摔倒了
Baby fall down!
那是…那是Consuela吗
Is that...? Is that Consuela?
小孩儿一个人走在街上
Baby all alone in street.
我把小孩儿带回家
I take baby home.
是我啊 Stewie 你不记得了吗
It's me. Stewie. Don't you remember?
你还给我们打扫过屋子咧
You used to clean for us.
我们还让你用加油站的厕所来着
We used to make you use the bathroom at the gas station.
嗨 是你啊
Hey, you!
呃 嗨 Ryan
Uh, hey, Ryan.
呃 这会儿不方便吗
Uh, bad time?
呃 太方便了
Um, perfect time.
进来吧 我正在给腿上涂油呢
Come on in. I was just oiling my legs.
那么 今晚有什么节目
So, hey, what's on for tonight?
这样的 我的牙医忘记锁办公室的门了
You know, my dentist leaves his office unlocked.
我觉得咱们可以进去搞点笑气
I was thinking we could do some nitrous
一氧化二氮俗称笑气 在牙医诊所常被用做麻醉剂
然后在那儿吃个饭
and then have dinner in there.
听着 Ryan 你是个大好人
Look, Ryan, you're a great guy and everything,
可我不喜欢你这个样子
but I don't like you in that way.
我是说 有些事情我乐意和你做
I mean, there are some things that I would do with you,
可我并没有那种想法
but my heart wouldn't be in it.
你在说什么呀
What are you talking about?
就是说你喜欢我 想做我男朋友
That you like me, and you want to be my boyfriend.
你以为我是同性恋吗
You think I'm gay?
你是从哪儿听到的
Where did you get that?
呃 呃 你想要吻我
Uh, uh, you-you tried to kiss me.
Peter 我不是同性恋
Peter, I'm not gay.
你这是哪根筋不对了
What the hell's the matter with you?
听着 听着 让我…让我这么和你说吧
Look, look, look, let me... let me put it to you this way.
我被你吸引的方式
I'm attracted to you in the way
就像男人被女人吸引 可我不是同性恋
that a man is attracted to a woman, but I'm not gay.
当你生活在好莱坞 你就会明白
When you live out in Hollywood, you learn
人生不过是沿途遇见许多不同的
that life is about different spirits and energies
心灵和能量
you meet along the way.
我只是认为我们的心灵可以交织 你明白吗
I just thought maybe our spirits could intertwine, you know?
我们的能量可以交融
Our energies could merge.
好比我的心灵可以进入你的能量
Like my spirit could go up inside your energy.
演艺圈里我还有很多要学的
I- I have so much to learn about show business.
可你知道吗
But you know what?
我绝不会被那个人真正吸引
I could never really be attracted to somebody
他给我贴上了"同性恋"和"直男"的标签
who uses labels like "gay" and "straight."
也许你该走了
Maybe you should just go.
好吧 好吧 稍等一下
Well-Well, now, wait a second.
你这是什么意思
What do you mean?
没戏了
This isn't working.
我曾经想的美好
It was a nice thought,
不过现在觉得我们应该各走各的路了
but I think we should go our separate ways.
不 Ryan 我现在明白了
No, Ryan. I get it now.
你想让我怎么做都行
I can be what you want.
我们可以…Peter
We could... Peter.
别勉强自己
Don't embarrass yourself.
你得放下这一切
You need to just let this go.
- 挠痒痒 挠痒痒 - 不 Peter 别这样
- Tickle fight! Tickle fight! - No, Peter, no!
- 挠痒痒 挠痒痒 挠痒痒… - Peter 别这样
- Tickle fight! Tickle fight! Tickle fight... - Peter, no! No!
老天爷啊…
Oh, my God...
你该走了
It's time for you to leave.
我能改变
I can change.
我很抱歉 Peter 我们之间结束了
I'm sorry, Peter. We're done.
我们再也不可以说话了
We can never talk again.
这儿有个手机还可以常联系
Here's a cell phone so we can always talk.
你们这里没有浴缸玩具吗
Don't you guys have any tub toys?
这个给你 拨浪鼓
Here. Is rattle.
这只是一瓶处方药
This is prescription medication.
而且标签上写的还不是你的名字
And it's not even your name on the label.
这…这又是什么
What... What is this?
这浴缸里有什么
What's in this tub?
- 是地瓜 - 什么地瓜
- Is jicama. - Jicama?
那这个又是…这个…这个…
And what is...? What...? What...?
这是个鸡腿
This is a chicken leg.
你还要用这做汤吗
Are you also making soup?
为成人礼准备的
For quinceañera.
拉丁裔女孩15岁生日的成人礼
大聚会 好多人
Big party. Many peoples.
老天呐
Oh, my God.
来了一只狗
Hay un perro aqui.
来了一只狗吗
Doggy es aqui?
我敢说你们这些人都不看George Lopez的
I bet even you guys don't watch George Lopez.
墨西哥裔美国单口相声演员
Consuela?
嗨 我是Brian啊
Hey, it's Brian.
我在找Stewie
I'm-I'm looking for Stewie.
不 这里没有小孩儿
No, no baby aqui.
我在你的汤里撒尿了
I peed in your soup.
15岁生日快乐
Happy 15th birthday.
顺便说一句
Which, by the way,
这在现实世界里根本不算什么特殊场合
is not a special occasion in the normal world.
Stewie 真急死我了
Stewie, I've been worried sick.
你到这儿来是干嘛呢
What the hell are you doing here?
Brian 你怎么找到我的
Brian? How did you find me?
我用鼻子闻的 但总是忘记这么做
I used my nose, which I always forget about.
咱们走吧
Come on, let's go.
不 我不回去 不能
No, I'm not going back! I can't!
他们会气疯的
They're gonna be mad at me!
我没告诉任何人
I didn't tell anyone.
你…你没有吗
You... you didn't?
我没有
No, I didn't.
我想了想 老实说
Look, I thought about it, and to be honest,
应该是我的错 不该把你单独留在车里
it's probably my fault for leaving you alone in the car.
要是你答应我再也不那么做了 我什么也不说了
And if you promise never to do it again, I won't say anything.
好的 我答应
Okay, I promise.
- 我的小孩儿 - 什么
- My baby! - What?
我说 放手
I say, let go of me.
Consuela 我们要走了
Consuela, we're leaving.
我的小孩儿
My baby!
哎 她说了是她的小孩儿 伙计
Hey, she says it's her baby, man.
现在 滚出去
Now, get out of here.
是我的小孩儿 Ernesto
Is my baby. Ernesto.
不 我不叫…我不叫Ernest…
No, I'm not... I'm not Ernest...
好吧 这情况挺复杂的
Okay, this is so messed up right now.
我本来不想这么做
I did not want to have to do that.
在那之前他们对我都挺好的
They were very nice to me up until then.
Peter 别再往窗外看了
Peter, stop staring out the window.
Ryan走了
Ryan's gone.
他拍完电影已经搬走了
He finished his movie, he's moved out.
我怎么瞎了眼呢
How could I have been so blind?
我怎么对他的付出视而不见呢
How could I not have seen what he offered?
我觉得整件事都很奇怪
I think the whole thing was very strange.
他觉得你很奇怪
He thought you were strange!
- 怎么着 - 随你怎么说
- How about that? - Whatever.
我无能为力 只是想知道…
I just can't help but wonder...
还能再遇见他吗
will I ever see him again?
中文字幕: zurica 校对: wudixny 注释: wudixny zurica 后期: zurica 压制: zurica @familyguy贴吧字幕组